Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Five hundred years ago
in Yongzhou
the young snake-catcher A Xuan
saved a white snake in a young woman's form
by giving up his own life.
Five hundred years passed.
Now it's the Song dynasty.
Wherever he is.
whatever he's like.
whether or not he remembers me.
I have to find him.
We are free!
I'll be back.
Wait for me.
Because”.
I remember.
Sister-
see these mountains?
These stones?
They haven't changed.
But the people of the village
are all gone.
To attain immortality
we practiced for hundreds of years.
At last we see the fruits of that.
You want to throw it all away?
Verta!
Say you find him.
How long can you be together?
Verta-
you're right.
Human life is like dew.
It lasts but a moment.
It's for that reason
I want to find him.
To repay his kindness.
When he passes.
I'll have done that
and can move on from this obsession!
Then
we can return to our self-cultivation.
Verta?
White Snake: Afloat
Lantern Festival
Lantern Festival Miss!
Miss!
Miss-
you dropped your hairpin!
Thank you. young sir.
This hairpin
looks quite precious.
It is.
Thank you for finding it.
We mustn't ever lose it.
You seem familiar. Miss.
Where are you from?
It's a long story.
But young sir-
what is your name?
Where are you from?
My surname is Xu
and my given name Xian.
I'm from Lin'an.
You're called Xu Xian.
Yes...
Dr Xu!
I sent for you urgently.
And you're here chatting?
- See you. Dr Xu! Take care!
You know-
My brother-in-law
was just a kid when I met him.
Now that he's married
and to such a great woman-
I've done my duty to his sister.
It's true.
For such a bride to appear out of nowhere
is so lucky it's almost spooky.
Let's go.
The wedding night is a golden time!
Husband.
Beloved.
Red threads bind. together forever.
Marital bliss. joy everlasting.
Life is a dream
and a lifetime like dew.
Seas might dry and stones decay
but our love is eternal.
This I solemnly swear.
The demons are coming!
I'm a demon.
Being with me can only hurt you.
Blanca!
A Xuan!
That jade hairpin-
good idea to bury it.
Verta!
You're here?
I've been here all night.
A fresh breeze and nature for a bed.
I love it.
But it's your wedding night.
What are you doing up so early?
I was just making a vow
to be a devoted wife and forgo the magic arts.
Let's keep away from the spirit world
and live peacefully with people
peacefully for one lifetime.
The magic arts weren't easy to master.
You can forgo them
but I'll still use them.
Verta-
just one request.
Please don't make trouble.
Sister-
must you do this?
Use a little magic
and jewels. good land and a nice house
could be yours.
Why live a hard life in this shabby place?
Sister-
magic is exciting in the moment.
But doesn't it always lead us
into terrible trouble?
Sister-
You finally got your wish
and married him.
But this Xu Xian-
is he really A Xuan's reincarnation?
Yes.
So for this guy
you cut off the road to immortality.
Is it worth it?
It is.
Don't run!
Stand still.
Xian!
Cold Food Festival
Get your mugwort cakes!
Cold Food Festival! Mugwort cakes!
Green as jade. soft as cotton.
Get your mugwort cakes!
Hey. you lovebirds-
shall we get some mugwort cakes?
Green as jade. soft as cotton.
Verta!
You'll tip the boat over!
Dr Xu. you're back at last!
My wife is vomiting and has the runs.
Many people have the same thing!
Dr Xu. quick. have a look.
My wife has it too.
She just fainted.
Let me see.
Help her inside.
I'll revive her with acupuncture.
Philtrum. fingertips. crown.
She's awake!
Everyone. stay calm.
Tell me the symptoms.
This epidemic has been so sudden.
None of the clinics can help.
There seems to be no cure.
But the medicine you give them-
isn't it making them better?
Blanca. this prescription
uses many pricey herbs
and is long term.
How can ordinary people afford it?
The herb shops keep raising prices.
That's so hateful.
Those pharmacies
only care about higher profits.
They don't care if people live or die.
What if we opened a pharmacy?
But... it's not like being a doctor.
You need capital.
The prescription needs tweaking.
This plague is so strange.
Li says they can't work out its origin.
Sister!
Dry spell. watch your candles!
Sister. just as you thought-
the plague moves west to east.
Case by case. it travels a straight line.
It's not natural.
Someone in this city
is poisoning people on purpose.
For poisoning. well water
is most convenient.
What a foul odor!
This well
has just been poisoned.
Sadly. I got here a moment too late
so failed to catch them.
Heading east...
which is the next well?
Four-Eyed Well at South Star Bridge.
An old Daoist in rustic robes
Gourd on back. cloth on head
Straw sandals. cloth socks. a humble man
Fix your lute? Cure your ills? Yes. I can!
Master. please wait!
People say that this plague
can only be cured by your pills.
This way.
We're begging you. sir!
Today I've sold out of pills.
Not one left.
Tomorrow morning. East Gate Water Market.
Be early. Wait for me there.
Thank you. Master.
Bust a ghost. catch a demon
Up willow-fringed lanes I stroll.
This well was just poisoned.
Maybe it was that travelling Daoist...
Rat demon!
1.000 cash a pop. so expensive!
It's a miracle cure. Be quiet.
Master. please open shop!
My family is dying.
The master is here!
We're saved!
Medicine for sale!
Master! I need a pill!
This rat demon
poisons the wells and sells the antidote.
Let's punish that little demon!
Sister. will you use your powers?
No worries. I'll take care of it.
You distract him. and watch me.
Sister-
you think you can just be
an ordinary mortal woman.
But in an emergency
how can you not use your powers?
Magic herbs. a guaranteed cure!
Pay up!
Bad stuff happens on a roll
Bad men one day pay the toll
A warning-
patch the hull before the boat sails.
That's it for today. closing shop.
These pills are quite unusual.
They use a herb
that tastes familiar.
But I can't think what it is.
Thank you. Beloved.
for all you've done.
You're so compassionate.
Didn't you say just now
that to open a pharmacy
we need more money?
Blanca. look-
Shop. herbs...
I've done the sums.
If we don't hire help
and run it ourselves
we'll still need
another 100 taels of silver.
Buy only official salt and wine.
Smuggle and risk a fine.
Silver...
The magistrate's office has plenty of that.
Everyone. look sharp!
Careful with that!
Dr Xu. your medicine cabinet!
Thank you! Just put it inside.
Dr Xu. where do we put the herbs?
On the counter.
Thank you!
Dr Xu-
where does the acupuncture model go?
Let me!
Dr Xu. don't-
let us do it.
Don't hurt your back.
Miss Blanca. where do you want these?
In the corner.
Sure.
Miss Blanca. and this?
Over there.
Thank you so much!
Money makes the wheels go round.
Now you've got silver
the shop can have a grand opening!
Verta...
Enough. Sis.
- You've already spent it.
- Here's the sign.
- Look how happy your husband is.
- Thank you! Over here.
- Verta. no more trouble.
- Thank you all.
This is the last time.
That depends on my mood.
Verta!
Blanca. here's our sign.
This pharmacy of ours -
what will we call it?
Maybe one day I can be a doctor.
not a snake-catcher.
The Hall of Protection
Xian-
let's call it The Hall of Protection.
What do you think?
The Hall of Protection.
Great name. That's it!
I can fly. amazing!
The Wind's at our back!
Xian?
What is it?
Blanca!
For some reason. seeing this sign
gave me déjà-vu
of cliffs and mountains.
I was flying...
Blanca!
That herb in his pills-
I know where it's from.
In Nine Creeks and Eighteen Gullies.
on Dragon Well Peak.
there's a steep slope.
I've picked herbs there.
Xian. be careful!
Okay!
Xian!
Blanca!
We're...?
We're flying. Blanca!
It's true. Xian-
we're flying!
Xian!
Look at your straw cape!
Xian-
I'm sure it's your true heart
that moved the mountain gods
to save us like that.
Thank you. mountain gods.
The two of us-
Xu Xian and Blanca-
vow to the gods and spirits
to use these herbs
to cure illness and save lives.
The two of us-
Xu Xian and Blanca-
vow to the gods and spirits.
This silver heist is most strange.
I've three days to solve the crime.
The magistrate's really on my back.
Such a capable man as the magistrate
is that way because he's at his wit's end.
But
of course he'll have a plan.
Sheriff-
a monk is at the gate.
He's here to help crack the case.
A monk here to crack the case?
Ridiculous. get rid of him.
Wait!
This is the magistrate's plan.
Lin'an County Government
Name Am'fl'abha.
I'm Fahai. abbot of Jinshan Temple.
And you must be Sheriff Li.
Yes. Abbot. this way.
I came from Zhenjiang to Hangzhou
because I heard about the plague
and wanted to help.
The magistrate told me about the robbery.
So
Since I'm already here
I'll lend a hand.
Of course.
The case. it's a weird one.
No one has yet turned up any clues.
But rest assured
that now that I'm in charge
we'll naturally get to the bottom of it!
Previous investigations
showed no sign of a break-in.
It's like all that silver grew legs
and walked out!
Come!
Goldie.
sniff it out!
The thief came in the window.
through its narrow bars and down.
went straight for the silver
then went out the same way.
But how could anyone do that?
Open!
I won't fight over it with a beast.
"Master of Midnight"?
Abbot. it's medicinal herbs.
But what's a Master of Midnight?
It's another name for a rat.
It clearly wasn't a human crime.
The brand on this bag...
Sheriff Li-
please search the town
for a Daoist called Master of Midnight.
A Daoist?
For you.
Here.
Dr Xu has always been so generous.
I hear that to cure this plague
his wife put all her savings
into opening this clinic.
What's more
he's not making any profit.
He only covers his costs!
My brother-in-law's pharmacy
has been an instant success.
Business is booming. right?
To your credit. sir.
With such crowds
you have us patrolling here
in case that 'Master of Midnight'
shows his face here.
Shhh!
Be discreet.
Don't be scaring him off.
Of course.
Line up. everyone! Line up.
You're seeing a doctor. be civil.
Damn you. snake demon!
Interfering with my business.
And planting evidence too.
Just wait
and see what I have up my sleeve!
I'll expose you!
Move aside!
You! Grow eyes!
No jostling!
Crackers drive off disease.
The plague is finally over.
Dr Xu. hello!
Hello everyone.
Your good name draws us here.
Thank you all.
Firecrackers scare off disease.
Good health to all!
Brother-in-law!
Hello Sheriff Li-
you're here too.
On an early patrol I saw
how the Hall of Protection
was doing great business.
It's better for doctors
not to have great business.
You deserve to prosper!
Thank you all.
Sheriff Li-
a letter for you.
Xian!
Blanca! Verta!
Good news!
A reply!
Look. a reply!
A few days ago I was thinking
that with business so good
we should put on an opera
to celebrate!
Hangzhou's top opera troupe
has to be
Precious Jade Workshop of Sandskin Lane.
Precious Jade Workshop?
Xian. let me just say
Their Moon over West Wing-
now that's great opera.
Sister. what's wrong?
Today's weather
Makes me sleepy.
Where's Red Maid?
Late spring weather
Makes me sleepy
Where is my Red Maid?
My!
A guest?
Bravo!
Go away!
Miss-
the temple has another visitor.
How reckless.
Ah!
A Boddhisatva come to earth!
Stop blathering.
This is our Miss Cui.
To see such a woman-
is she not
a stunning beauty?
Bravo!
Sister-
What is it?
The actress playing Red Maid-
I know her.
This demon-
it's her.
Five hundred years ago
the maker of my jade hairpin
was the boss of Precious Jade Workshop.
Now
she's in Hangzhou
managing an opera troupe.
Over the floor
Lies 3 flowery carpet of rouge.
Don't spoil
This elegant scene.
Look at our lady's face-
It's as fine as silk.
That's one lucky scholar.
Bravo!
When the moon rises
And the door is set ajar
The flowers are a-tremble
And the Beauty isn't far.
"When the moon rises..."
I should go when the moon is up.
"And the door is set ajar..."
She'll open her door
"The flowers are a-tremble
And the Beauty isn't far..."
She wants me to jump the wall.
Miss-
I'm coming!
Beast'.
It's me!
Why are you hugging me?
I was faint with hunger
and grabbed you by mistake.
Grabbed me by mistake?
I think you
are a beast by nature
disguised as a scholar.
Beast in disguise!
Beast
in disguise!
Bravo!
Blanca
Precious Jade Workshop is great.
Can't eat. can't sleep. lovelorn cries...
If patience you have never tried
And on sincerity cannot rely
Yearning won't give way to sweet sighs.
Come one come all!
Hey. Xu Xian-
come on. let's go!
Bravo!
Dr Xu. closing up?
Yes.
And Miss Blanca?
She had some things to do
so she's gone home.
I see.
Good sir.
your aura is black.
There's a dark miasma about you.
Demon spirits live in your home!
Um. Mister-
how is that possible?
Let me pass.
We were fated to meet
so I'll give you this talisman
to protect your life.
Okay. I've got it.
Blanca. I'm home.
You're back.
Blanca. what's wrong?
Here. sit down.
Sister!
Blanca.
Xian-
I suddenly felt dizzy.
Here.
I'll check your pulse.
Sister-
he brought this home.
What?
Xian-
take this pulse too.
Blanca-
Did this just begin today?
Maybe you should go in and lie down.
What was...?
Xian-
rub my temples.
Blanca. has this happened before?
Yuck. so gross.
Honey. I'm okay.
Really?
Blanca. this sudden dizziness. it-
Xu Xian-
what's this?
This?
When I was on the way home
a fortune-teller forced it on me.
Why's it torn in two?
He said I had demons at home.
I ignored him.
What did this fortune-teller look like?
I didn't look that closely
but he had rat-like features.
He looked like a rat.
Blanca. are you feeling better?
Mr Monk!
Yesterday you came after me and I told you
I didn't steal the silver!
You little rat. Sneaky.
Yesterday. you ran away.
But if it wasn't you
then why was a bag of your pills there?
My up dragon recognizes all demons
and followed the scent of the medicine.
He's always right.
It really wasn't me!
I've been framed!
Whatever the case.
you demon. what are you doing here?
You can't be up to any good.
All demons
must be exterminated.
Mr Monk-
there's a demon over there too.
Go get it!
So-a snake demon!
Amitabha.
Cheap tricks.
Hangzhou is full of evil spirits.
Dragon Boat Festival
Go. Brother-in-Law!
Smash it. Brother-in-Law!
Yay!! Well done!
It's decreed that for Dragon Boat Festival
Hangzhou's wine shops will provide
realgar wine in celebration!
Use this realgar to make the wine.
I cast a spell on it
but keep that secret.
Yes-
to rid us of poison and plague
you exhaust yourself yet gain nothing.
Truly a great reverend.
And before you know it
the finish line was in sight
and my drum went boom boom boom.
Even the river dragons
came up for a look.
Do you see how. with the dragons' help.
our boat flew across the finish line.
What a man!
I can see how strong you are!
You are so discerning!
Perceptive too!
Look. the winning dragon boat
gets ten jars of realgar wine.
Drink up. everyone!
A toast!
Verta. have some realgar wine.
It keeps snakes and bugs at bay!
Here!
Not for me!
Sister-in-law!
Our family
owes you so much.
Come. you should drink a bowl.
Yes. Blanca. have a bowl! C'mon!
Blanca. Brother-in-Law
won this wine today as a prize.
Have some!
Sister. this is realgar wine!
I've been practising 1.000 years.
A little bit shouldn't hurt.
Brother-in-law! Husband!
Bravo!
Drink up! C'mon!
- The taste of realgar wine-
- Come. Blanca.
It doesn't appeal to me.
I'll use almond flower wine!
Let's sit down. Here.
Bottoms up!
Brother-in-law. you call that drinking?
Bravo!
Husband-
I feel faint. I'm going home.
Blanca. are you alright?
I'm okay.
Stay with Verta and Brother-in-Law
and enjoy the drinking.
Alright. I'll see you later.
Let's go. sister-in-law.
Let's go to Houchao Gate
and catch some shows.
Little bro. come with us!
You go.
I'd better go look after my wife.
Go then. Newly-weds!
Sister-in-law. come with me?
Sure.
A lotus bath. sweet flag flower brew
And gentle sunlight too.
Blanca?
She's not here?
What if she fell in?
Blanca!
Where are you?
Xian!
Blanca!
Verta!
His pulse is weak. I can't save him.
Hurry. help me!
Verta. where are you?
Xian!
Miss!
It's Hangzhou's top opera troupe!
Precious Jade Workshop of Sandskin Lane.
Revive-the-dead hocus pocus
is the sort of job we love.
Precious Jade Workshop!
Boss!
Cloak...
Pretty woman...
Woman warrior...
You want to save your husband-
hard and yet not hard.
The not hard part
is that I know how to save him.
Besides. you paid upfront
with a precious snake scale.
The hard part is yours.
Your husband-
a mortal-saw your true face
and his spirit fled in fright.
What remains
is seeping away.
Such a faint-hearted soul-
how's that going to work out for you?
It was my fault. not his.
I'll be more careful from now on.
Mortals
and demons-
not a natural pairing.
I fear future hardships
will be endless for you.
The future's the future.
Please save him!
Given our 500-year karmic connection...
Come with me!
There's a fairy grass that'll save him.
It grows on a steep cliff
in a cold place in the Northwest.
Mt Kunlun.
Mt Kunlun?
Yes.
Reviving such an unexceptional mortal is easy.
Just pick some fairy grass on Kunlun
and he'll be saved.
But to get there
is a journey
of three days and nights.
In the state he's in...
Found it!
It's this thing-
this incense burner.
See the tip of the burner?
That's Mt Kunlun.
I'll light this incense and send you there.
Where's the jade hairpin I made you?
Why aren't you wearing it?
Mt Kunlun is a very dangerous place.
Never mind.
As part of the deal. I'll throw in
a pair of swords.
You must return
before the incense burns down.
Once it's out. the road is cut.
Hurry there and back.
Go!
To save my husband
I need fairy grass.
Mountain gods. have mercy.
You demon!
How dare you come to Kunlun for fairy grass?
You think you can just come
and go as you please?
Right?
Lil' Bro-
that "right" was a bit off.
You need to convey authority.
That be like-
"Right?"
Stress. rise.
cut.
"Right..."?
Big Bro. that sound of mine-
light and long
is for mockery.
Right?
No.
No idea who she is. so why the scorn?
Lil' bro. don't underestimate the enemy.
Big Bro-
There's purpose to my mockery.
Where'd she go?
The demon fled!
Don't run. demon!
Cut her off.
So she was a snake demon.
Cranes eat snakes. right?
Little Bro. wrong again.
All creatures eat and are eaten.
We don't just eat snakes.
So snakes eat cranes?
Not exactly true either.
Cripes!
It's the Kunlun Crane Twins!
Demon. you won't get away!
Xian!
He lives. Pal-
we've got a new business deal.
In the future. if you run into trouble
come to Precious Jade Workshop.
What's this about?
He's still recovering.
Let him sleep.
Blanca!
Xian. are you okay?
Blanca-
I was in the strangest place just now.
You were there.
And the singer from Precious Jade Workshop too.
You were dreaming.
Dreaming...
Have some water.
That giant snake last night!
Blanca-
there's a giant snake in our pond.
A huge one. for real.
It's okay.
It was just a dream.
It was no dream.
It was real. Blanca.
It was in the pond.
Blanca. what should we do?
We need to move!
Let's move!
He's too scared to leave the house?
Sister-
this husband of yours is usually okay.
How'd he become such a scaredy-cat?
Nice looking but useless.
These swords aren't bad.
I want one.
Verta-
you can't blame him.
I turned into a giant snake
and he's just a mortal.
In a past life as A Xuan
he feared nothing at all.
Sister-
maybe with each reincarnation
he loses a little courage?
Verta-
he's my husband.
Don't mock him.
But what should I do now?
Heart sickness needs heart medicine.
But where can that be found?
I have a plan.
Listen...
You...
you're still a naughty girl.
Blanca-
that snake
was right here.
There's nothing in the pond.
Honey. careful!
You insisted I bring you here.
But that snake's definitely in there.
Go.
Snake!
Run. Blanca!
Run!
Run. fast!
Blanca-
run!
Brother-in-law?
Sister-in-law?
Anyone home?
To be so scared.
No snakes grow that big.
I'll get him drunk
and he'll sleep.
Nothing a drink won't cure.
Snake!
Snake?
Xu Xian! Blanca!
Snake!
Xu Xian!
Where...
Snake!
It's true!
Xu Xian! Blanca!
I'm coming!
Xu Xian!
Xu...
Verta!
Blanca!
I'm going to die!
Snake!
Eat... my... sword!
Blanca!
Xian-
you were right.
There really was a giant snake.
That you're okay
is all that matters.
Lucky.
Verta cut that snake in two.
I'm not exaggerating.
That snake. thick as a barrel
came crashing down like a mountain!
Staying calm and collected
I pulled out my precious sword.
unleashed my Dog Kung-fu-
Hou Xiaoyi. nice brocade.
Have some. Sheriff!
When you get married.
you can use it then.
Have a look!
Rubbish! Who would I marry...
Ah. but that sister-in-law of mine...
Sheriff. you were saying-
about the snake?
Uh I was about to say that my sister-in-law
suddenly whipped out her sword
and like lightning
cut that enormous snake in half!
What a woman.
Such beauty. such skill-
how can she just hang around unmarried?
Your sister-in-law is a formidable woman.
She deserves an excellent match.
So true.
House of Abundant Joy
Sister-in-law. believe me-
Hangzhou is full of good men.
Literati. martial types-we have them all.
Your matchmaking-leave it to me.
You're a big talker. Fine.
I'm curious.
I'll see for myself what this crowded city
offers in the way of men.
Sister-in-law.
here we go!
Enter!
Out!
Next.
Smalls.
Small.
Keep the line moving.
At the back. speed it up.
Hold up!
Get in there.
Go on!
There's more.
Just wait.
What an embarrassment.
Such a motley crew.
Sheriff. all the single men
from our area are here.
Keep looking. find more.
Amitabha. Sheriff Li.
Reverend Fahai. Amitabha.
Sheriff Li. I heard the guards saying
that at your home last night
a giant snake was killed.
Well. it was at my brother-in-law's place
and my sister-in-law killed it.
Reverend. want to meet her?
Today's her big day.
She's meeting suitors.
She's busy.
Stop there!
Spare me. please!
Reverend. you're a presentable fellow.
Listen. Reverend-
first. she's meeting potential matches
and you want to meet her.
It's karma. as you say.
Second. you want to meet Verta.
But those robes-not gonna work.
I've heard other monks say
Form is formlessness and formlessness form.
Whether monk form or police form
it's still form.
I didn't know you were so enlightened.
Let's go.
This way. please.
Maybe it'll be love at first sight
and you'll leave the monkhood.
That would be a meritorious. right?
Miss...
Amazing. Here's alive one.
Sit down.
Boss. what's going on in there?
Say something already!
You're sitting like a monk carved from wood.
Ami...
A...
You're called Verta. miss?
Yep. I have a sister called Blanca.
Her husband is Xu Xian of the Hall of Protection.
And you. what's your name?
How old are you? Where are you from?
I...
I'm from Jinshan.
A... A...
my name is...
it's...
Goodness you're slow.
Can barely spit out your own name.
C'mon.
Sheriff Li says
you killed a huge snake last night
That's right.
And it first appeared at the Dragon Boat Festival?
You can't fool around with realgar wine.
How'd you know what it was?
I just did.
Monk!
Yes?
Why did you just shout?
I saw a monk down there.
Strutting about. accosting people. brazen.
I just called to him.
Brother-in-law!
That's the masked woman we saw.
So the realgar wine was drunk after all.
Some monk. coming a-courting.
Shameless
but pretty skilful.
When I see that Li
I'll give him a piece of my mind.
What? She jumped out the window?
My sister-in-law does have a temper.
No idea when she'll be back.
Reverend. did you
say something to offend her?
Her sister
is married to Dr Xu?
Her sister is very beautiful.
But she has a weak constitution.
At the Dragon Boat Festival
just drinking a little realgar wine
made her dizzy.
These sisters are really something.
Suitors all day and not one passed.
How is Verta going to find a husband?
Xian!
Blanca!
What's so urgent?
Calling me home like this.
I'm making you some clothes
and was buying thread-
A monk?
He insists our house has demons.
I told him
about the giant snake
but said we'd killed it.
Greetings. Dr Xu.
Greetings.
He's spouting nonsense.
Why didn't you chase him off?
Here. these are for you.
Thank you!
Blanca. but you see.
he's the abbot of Jinshan Temple-
Fahai...
A luminary. I couldn't chase him off.
Besides. if I did
he'd get mad and tell people we have demons.
What can we do?
Fahai of Jinshan Temple?
You've heard of him?
He insists on meeting you.
Then he says he'll go.
The nerve.
I know! But...
he won't leave our place
unless you return and speak to him.
Okay.
I'll go see this monk fellow.
In broad daylight. all's well
and he comes pestering people
about demons in the home.
Xian. wait in the courtyard. Don't move.
Blanca!
Xian-
I'm afraid that in soon
I'll be giving him a piece of my mind.
If you're there. he'll lose face.
Big Monk-
you come here out of the blue
to our humble home.
The Xu home has demons.
Demons here? No way.
Being a mortal. Xu Xian can't see them.
Are you not a mortal too. Reverend?
Are you not flesh and blood?
Of course I'm a mortal.
And what's your proof
that we have demons?
Demon-subduing magic weapons!
Rise!
Go!
No!
Blanca!
Xu Xian!
This is your beloved wife.
Blanca?
Blanca!
Let her go.
Reverend! let my wife go!
Reverend-
Let my wife go!
Reverend!
Xu Xian. you're helping demons!
Reverend. she's my wife.
Xu Xian!
Amitabha. forgive me
the desires of this world. born of karma.
A desirous world. full of misery and discontent.
Allie well. watch your candles...
Blanca! Verta! Brother-in-law!
I...
In the future if you run into trouble
come to Precious Jade Workshop.
Precious Jade Workshop.
Sandskin Lane.
My days are filled with wine
My mornings with flowers fine
I dance and sing and joy is mine
What happened?
Dr Xu asked this masterly monk
home to perform a ritual.
Then I saw Xu Xian
bring Miss Blanca home.
She'd become a snake!
Is Miss Blanca a demon?
That's Blanca's sister!
Could she be a demon too?
Demons!
Demons! Run!
Sister!
Dr Xu-
you've come with an offer
for a trade.
Scary.
Do you know what this is?
It's Reverend Fahai's
golden bowl. right?
That's one vicious monk.
What'd you do to upset him?
Fahai's magic weapon is inside.
It's a Golden Updragon.
It's as powerful as lightning.
If it smells something
it'll fixate on it.
This beast
will scour the world
without tiring.
Even I am scared of it.
Please help me.
I am a businesswoman after all
and you're an old customer.
Come.
Sister!
You can't kill it
with poison. fire or water.
There's only one method.
You provoke the beast
into an attack.
After he strikes
he morphs back into Buddha pearls
and waits quietly in his bowl.
But...
who should he attack?
Naturally not me.
Them?
Useless things.
Therefore
it can only be you. Dr Xu.
Me?
Only by putting your life
under this attack
can you save your demon wife.
I think this exchange
would even please the abbot Fahai.
Are you willing. Dr Xu?
A life for a life. It's just.
I'm willing.
Good.
Although you are weak
you still have a will of iron.
We'll do the deal.
This flute-
blow lightly and it's just a flute.
But if you expend your vital essence
and play it loud and high
you call forth its magic.
When the Updragon attacks
play it without stopping
until the music
lures him back into the bowl.
The stronger the enemy
the more essence you lose.
Dr Xu. your vital essence
won't go to waste.
It's exactly what I collect for my fee.
But
once you expend so much of it
you may not survive.
Even if you do survive
you'll be weak
and badly affected.
Dr Xu. are you still willing?
Although my wife is a demon
we love each other deeply.
She is so devoted
and never lets me down.
One day's vow. a lifetime of love
I'm weak
but I want to repay her love.
Good.
It's a deal.
Blanca!
Sister?
Sister.
I'm here.
Blanca?
Blanca!
Dr Xu!
Dr Xu. you'd better run.
You've been reported.
They're looking for you.
Me?
Yeah.
They say you're harbouring demons.
Your wife
and Verta.
Verta...
Where'd they go?
No idea.
Last night
Verta turned into
a terrifying monster
and scared us to death.
What's that?
Dr Xu. you... you...
Help! Demons!
Jinshan Temple
Reverend-
please let them go.
I'm returning this golden bowl to you.
They never harmed anyone.
Please have mercy!
Have mercy!
Today they do no harm.
But tomorrow they will.
No.
Reverend. they'd never.
I offer my life as security.
Demons are demons.
Isn't harming people in their nature?
They would never. I...
Xu Xian-
I want to know
how you turned the Golden Updragon
back into Buddha pearls.
Uh...
It had to be with the help
of a powerful demon
Xu Xian-
you're deep in the demons' spell.
Colluding with them
hand in glove.
Reverend. it's not true.
My wife and I have done nothing bad.
I...
Why not stay at Jinshan Temple
for a short while.
I'm sure those demons
will come looking to save you
and I'll annihilate them.
No!
Reverend!
Mid-Autumn Festival
Sister-in-law!
Verta! What're you doing here?
They're after you...
You're the sheriff.
Why not arrest me?
I...
I'm a demon.
Hurry. go.
Even seeing you like this
I still want to call you
Sister-in-law.
Run away!
Sister-in-law?
Brother-in-law!
Verta!
Did you say
he went to Jinshan Temple
and is staying there?
Yes.
That's why these last few days
we couldn't find him in Hangzhou.
We'd rather not involve you.
But we're at wits' end
so we've come to ask you.
Please forgive us.
Sister-in-law...
Sister has been so distressed.
But good for him.
He'll be so happy at the temple.
Verta!
Sister-
didn't you say
that he took you home
while the monk was there
setting a trap?
They're on the same side!
Xu Xian isn't that sort of person!
Person?
Isn't that something people do?
He totally. absolutely
brought home that monk
and then took Blanca to him.
But. but he...
Sister-
let's attack Jinshan Temple.
We'll drag Xu Xian out and ask him!
No. don't do it.
You have no idea.
That Fahai's magic powers
are of the highest order.
You mustn't do it!
So what if we do?
A fight will prove who's more powerful.
It's come to this
and you're trying to shield him?
I was just making a vow
to be a devoted wife
and forgo the magic arts.
Let's keep away from the spirit world
and live among ordinary people
peacefully for a lifetime.
This Xu Xian-
is he really all that A Xuan was?
A Xuan?
Why's that name so familiar?
Sister-
Sister. what's wrong?
In my belly
there's a child.
Double Ninth Festival
Here it comes!
This year's tide surfers
include some Jinshan Temple monks.
Real hotshots!
Yeah. a floating Jinshan Temple. amazing.
Tell the monk Fahai
that Verta awaits him in Hangzhou.
Demon!
What's that?
A giant flood dragon?
Yes. Master. 3 huge green snake.
Those brazen demons!
I need to return to Hangzhou.
Keep a close eye on Xu Xian.
We'll deal with him when I'm back.
Yes.
The moon rises o'er the sea
From far away you see it too.
Beloved-
I can't even see the moon.
How are you faring?
Verta!
You ingrate!
I'll thrash you first
to get it out of my system.
My sister was so good to you.
Verta-
Why'd you let the monk get to her!
When she left. wounded-
instead of looking for her.
you came here!
Verta-
Xu Xian-
you don't deserve her true love for you.
Verta. let me explain...
No!
Xu Xian. I won't listen to you.
What you have to say. say it to Blanca.
She's pregnant.
Pregnant?
My beloved is pregnant?
She's pregnant! Pregnant!
Xian!
Brother-in-law. you've come too!
Did you know
that Blanca is pregnant?
Follow them.
Sister!
Won't you turn and see your husband?
Beloved!
Blanca. I'm back!
It's my fault.
I did wrong.
Blanca!
It was me who was wrong.
I'm a demon.
I'm out of line to crave mortal bliss.
No. Blanca!
How can the child in your belly be wrong?
Your child.
our child
wants to be born. that's not out of line.
That's definitely not out of line.
True-
this child belongs.
He'll come into the world happily. peacefully.
Blanca.
Reverend-
how'd you follow us here?
Each to its path. that's heaven's way.
How can demons and humans co-exist?
It violates the way of heaven
and rules of the world
Reverend. how can a monk
be so cold-hearted and merciless?
You bald jerk. my sister never hurt anyone.
What heavenly way did she break?
You declare an earthly rule
and then it's an earthly rule?
According to who? Did anyone consult us?
Why should we follow your stinking rules?
We'll do as we please!
Reverend!
Xu Xian-
You saw her human form
and were bewitched again.
Remember how she became a giant snake
and scared you half to death?
Reverend-
since you bring that up
perhaps right here and now
I'll return to my original form.
Xu Xian can decide for himself.
Blanca!
Red threads bind.
Forever sworn.
Life is a dream. a lifetime like dew.
Even if the seas dry up and stones decay
our love will survive.
This I solemnly swear.
And this vow
is engraved on my heart.
I'll never regret it.
Blanca!
I've exhausted my store of good will.
Although Buddha is compassionate
it seems only the lion's roar
will shake you out of your delusions!
Sinful beasts!
Diamond Lion's Roar!
Sister!
Blanca!
Xian!
No!
Sister!
Xian!
The Dharma is limitless
and without end!
Go!
So this demon
has a child in her belly.
Star of Learning!
Could the baby in her belly
be the Star's mortal incarnation?
Can such unnatural thing be possible?
And those two beasts?
Xu Xian!
Reverend!
My brother-in-law-
what's happening to him?
I don't know which demon
taught him that.
To save that White Snake
he almost used up his vital essence.
Brother-in-law!
And... the sisters?
Where are they?
You!
Verta saved Blanca
and they left.
Xian!
I'll take him to the temple
and save him.
Sheriff Li-
help me get him there.
Okay.
Sister.
Look what I found for him!
Sister?
Lantern Festival
Blanca?
Verta.
I'm guessing from your dress
you'll look for him at the temple.
Yes.
To find your husband
you'd abandon your sister?
It looks like
I couldn't if I tried.
Sister-
was this time in the mortal realm
worth it?
Worth it or not-
to remember is enough.
Verta-
we'll take a trip to Jinshan Temple.
Sure. however strong and heavy it is
we'll overturn it!
You and I
will tear it apart.
A Light Chaser Animation Film
In empty rooms. a whiff of fragrance
On the old stage. memories linger
Where did all the people go?
Willow fronds undulate in the breeze
Emerald waves. jade lily pads
A solitary flute
Dewy moonlight
Mournful sighs
So many things. so much feeling
So much sorrow and joy
All just tears in the rain
Washed away without a trace
How brief is life
How eternal is the world
Things change. people go
Stories flow like a river
A mulberry pole. a magnolia paddle
Bai Causeway at West Lake
Green Snake. White Snake
Xu Xian and Blanca
A story of Tang times
Recorded in the Song
Alive to this day
The legend continues
The sounds and sights of our time
The sorrows and joys too
Infinite variations in our fleeting lives
Have given us this time together
This big world is not our own
We dance like mayflies in the wind
A cup of wine. along way
Remembering willows by the lake
This big world is not our own
We dance like mayflies in the wind
A cup of wine. along way
Remembering willows by the lake
Big Bro
this little demon has blown us
to a place where even birds don't poo.
Lil' Bro...
You're still not taking this seriously.
We two are still here. anyway.
Big Bro. that's dumb.
Aren't we birds?
No.
♪ Once in a thousand years ♪
♪ Once in a thousand years. no regrets ♪
♪ That soft "I'll love you forever" in my ear ♪
♪ For that alone. I'd risk heartbreak ♪
♪ The rain grieves. the wind weeps ♪
♪ A lingering dream. a faraway love ♪
♪ A West Lake made of my tears ♪
♪ Let us ignite into a single flame ♪
♪ Once in a thousand years ♪
♪ Once in a thousand years. no regrets ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm